AoM Publications 5289 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series X: Business Policy and Strategy Division, 1975-2011
  - Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, 1978-1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Item 24: Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      By Academy of Management. Autumn 1986. Item is in English.
    - Item 25: Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Item 26: Business Policy & Planning, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      By Newsletter Editor: Harvey Hegarty. Spring 1978. Item is in English.
    - Item 27: Business Policy & Planning, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      By Nesletter Editor: Harvey Hegarty. Autumn 1978. Item is in English.
    - Item 28: Business Policy & Planning, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      By Newsletter Editor: Harvey Hegarty. Spring 1979. Item is in English.
    - Item 29: Business Policy & Planning, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      By Anne S. Huff. Autumn 1981. Item is in English.
    - Item 30: Business Policy & Planning, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      By Editor: Anne S. Huff. Spring 1982. Item is in English.
    - Item 31: Business Policy & Planning, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      By Editor: Anne S. Huff. Autumn 1982. Item is in English.
    - Item 32: Business Policy & Planning, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      By Editor: Anne S. Huff. Spring 1983. Item is in English.
    - Item 33: Business Policy & Planning, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      By Editor: Anne S. Huff. Autumn 1983. Item is in English.
    - Item 34: Business Policy & Planning, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      By Editor: Anne S. Huff. Spring 1984. Item is in English.
    - Item 35: Business Policy & Planning, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      By editor, R. Duane Ireland. Autumn 1984. Item is in English.
    - Item 36: Business Policy & Planning, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      By Editor, R. Duane Ireland. Summer 1985. Item is in English.
  - Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, 1987-1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      By Academy of Management. Spring 1987. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 3: Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      By Academy of Management. Autumn 1987. Item is in English.
    - Item 4: Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 5: Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      By Academy of Management. Spring 1988. Item is in English.
    - Item 6: Busines Policy and Planning Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 7: Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      By Academy of Management. Autumn 1988. Item is in English.
    - Item 8: Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 9: Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      By Academy of Management. Spring 1989. Item is in English.
    - Item 10: Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 11: Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 12: Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      By Academy of Management. Autumn 1989. Item is in English.
    - Item 13: Business Policy and Planning, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 14: Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      By Academy of Management. Spring 1990. Item is in English.
    - Item 15: Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 16: Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 17: Business and Policy Planning newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      By Academy of Management. Autumn 1990. Item is in English.
    - Item 18: Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 19: Busines Policy and Planning Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      By Academy of Management. Spring 1991. Item is in English.
    - Item 20: Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: BPS, Newsletter, Rough Drafts and Application, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      By University of Southern Maine; School of Business, Economics & Management. Autumn 1989. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: BPS, Newsletter, Rough Draft and Application, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      By University of Southern Maine; School of Business, Economics & Management. Spring 1990. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: BPP Division Secretary and Newsletter Editor Application, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      By Deborah J Bickford. August 23, 1989. Item is in English.
    - Item 4: The University of Dayton Letter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      By Deb Bickford. October 29, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
      By Academy of Management. Fall 1991. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Item 3: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
      By Academy of Management. Spring 1992. Item is in English.
    - Item 4: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Item 5: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
      By Academy of Management. Fall 1992. Item is in English.
    - Item 6: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Item 7: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
      By Academy of Management. Spring 1993. Item is in English.
    - Item 8: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
      By Academy of Management. Fall 1993. Item is in English.
    - Item 9: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Item 10: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
      By Academy of Management. Spring 1994. Item is in English.
    - Item 11: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Item 12: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
      By Academy of Management. Fall 1994. Item is in English.
    - Item 13: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
      By Academy of Management. Spring 1995. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
      By Academy of Management. Spring 1996. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
      By Academy of Management. Fall 1996. Item is in English.
    - Item 4: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
      By Academy of Management. Spring 1997. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Item 6: Busines Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Item 7: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
      By Academy of Management. Fall 1998. Item is in English.
  - Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, 1995-2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 2: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 3: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 4: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
      By Academy of Management. Fall 1995. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 6: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 7: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 8: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 9: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 10: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 11: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 12: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 13: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 14: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 15: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 16: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 17: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 18: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 19: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 20: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
      By Academy of Management. Fall 2000. Item is in English.
    - Item 21: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 22: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
      By Business Policy and Strategy Division. Spring 2003. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Item 3: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Item 4: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
      By Business Policy and Strategy Division. Fall 2002. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Item 6: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Item 7: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
      By Business Policy and Strategy Division. Spring 2002. Item is in English.
    - Item 8: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Item 9: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Item 10: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
      By Business Policy and Strategy Division. Fall 2001. Item is in English.
    - Item 11: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Item 12: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
      By Business Policy and Strategy Division. Fall 2003. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Item 3: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
      By Business Policy and Strategy Division. Spring 2004. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Item 3: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Item 4: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
      By Business Policy and Strategy Division. Fall 2004. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Item 6: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: 25th Annual International Conference, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
      By Strategic Management Society. October 23- 26, 2005. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: 25th Annual International Conference, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
      By Strategic Management Society. October 23 - 26, 2005. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
      By Business Policy and Strategy Decision. Spring 2005. Item is in English.
    - Item 4: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Item 5: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
      By Business Policy and Strategy Decision. Fall 2005. Item is in English.
    - Item 6: Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Business Policy and Strategy Spring Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
      By Business Policy and Strategy Decision. Spring 2006. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Business Policy and Strategy Spring Newsleter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Item 3: Business Policy and Strategy Spring Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Spring Newsletter, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Fall Newsletter, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Newsletter, 2010 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Spring Newsletter, 2011 (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Series XI: Careers Division, 1978-2006
  Was formerly the Career Interest Group
  - A Reivew of the Career Interest Group, 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: A Review of the Career Interest Group: A Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
      By Raymond Hill. Item is in English.
  - Careers Division: Annual Meeting, 1982-1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Careers Interest Group Pre-conference Workshop Program (Draft), Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
      By James G. Clawson. December 27, 1982. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Careers Division Workshop, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
      By James Werbel. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: Careers Division Preconference Workshop, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
      By Allan Bird. Item is in English.
    - Item 4: Careers Division Preconference Workshop, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Item 5: Careers Division Preconference Workshop, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Item 6: A Cruise Party on the "Beautiful Ohio", Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
      By Academy of Management. August 12, 1996. Item is in English.
    - Item 7: Networking Questionarre, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
      By Academy of Management. No date. Item is in English.
  - Constitution Revision, Division Status, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: Academy of Management Career Interest Group, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
      By Academy of Management. Postcard. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: The Academy of Management - 1983, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
      By Ray Hill. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: Academy of Management Career Interest Group, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Item 4: Academy of Management - 1983, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Item 5: Academy of Management Career Interest Group, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Item 6: Academy of Management - 1983, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Item 7: Constitution of the Careers Division of the Academy of Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
      By Academy of Management. Third Draft. Item is in English.
    - Item 8: Ballot for Approval/Disapproval of Division Constitution and Bylaws, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
      By Don Bowen. Email. Item is in English.
    - Item 9: Constitution of the Careers Division of the Academy of Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Item 10: Ballot for Approval/Disapproval of Division Constitution and Bylaws, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
      By Don Bowen. Item is in English.
  - The Career Forum, 1989-2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: the career forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
      By Careers Division of the Academy of Management. Fall 1989. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: the career forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
      By Careers Division of the Academy of Management. Fall 1995. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: Letter to Careers Division Members, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
      By Jay Mahoney. June 16, 1997. Item is in English.
    - Item 4: Careers Division of the Academy of Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
      By Careers Division of the Academy of Management. Spring 1999. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: The career forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Item 6: The career forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Item 7: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
      By Careers Division, Academy of Management. Fall 2000. Item is in English.
    - Item 8: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Item 9: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Item 10: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
      By Careers Division, Academy of Management. Spring 2001. Item is in English.
    - Item 11: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Item 12: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Item 13: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
      By Careers Division, Academy of Management. Fall 2002. Item is in English.
    - Item 14: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Item 15: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - The Career Forum and Additional Publications, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: The career forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
      By Careers Division of the Academy of Management. Fall 1998. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: The career forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 3: The career forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 4: Careers Division Preconference Workshop, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
      By Allan Bird. August 1996. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: From the Chair of the Careers Division, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
      By Careers Division of the Academy of Management. Item is in English.
  - The Career Forum, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 2: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 3: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 4: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
      By Careers Division, Academy of Management. Fall 2003. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 6: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
      By Careers Division, Academy of Management. Spring 2003. Item is in English.
    - Item 7: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 8: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - The Career Forum, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
      By Careers Division of the Academy of Management. Fall 2004. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 3: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 4: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
      By Careers Division of the Academy of Management. Spring 2005. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 6: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 7: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
      By Careers Division of the Academy of Management. Fall 2005. Item is in English.
    - Item 8: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 9: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 10: The Career Forum Abstracts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 11: The Career Forum Abstracts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 12: The Career Forum Abstracts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 13: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
      By Careers Division of the Academy of Management. Spring 2006. Item is in English.
    - Item 14: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 15: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 16: The Career Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 17: The Career Forum Abstracts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 18: The Career Forum Abstracts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 19: The Career Forum Abstracts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Series XII: Conflict Management Division, 1987-2007
  Was formerly the Power Negotiation and Conflict Management Division
  - Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, 1987-1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 2: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 3: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 4: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
      By Academy of Management. Fall 1990. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 6: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 7: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
      By Academy of Management. Summer 90. Item is in English.
    - Item 8: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 9: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 10: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
      By Academy of Management. Winter 1989. Item is in English.
    - Item 11: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 12: Powe Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 13: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
      By Academy of Management. Fall 1989. Item is in English.
    - Item 14: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 15: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 16: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 17: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 18: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 19: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
      By Academy of Management. Fall 1988. Item is in English.
    - Item 20: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 21: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 22: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
      By Academy of Management. June 1988. Item is in English.
    - Item 23: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 24: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 25: Power Negotiation and Conflict Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
      By Academy of Management. December 1987. Item is in English.